I'm thrifting with me. Something about
wearing used socks is just so comforting
to me. And they had the best sock
selection here. This place is literally
the size of three football fields. My
first non-sock find of the day was these
gorgeous palm tree embroidered jeans.
And then I found this beautiful floral
blouse. I don't know what baddie donated
every single one of her fairy tops, but
they genuinely just kept going. And then
I found these adorable Victoria's Secret
mini shorts. There were so many purses,
I got overwhelmed. I ended back up in
the sock section. I thought that these
floral mini shorts were so adorable.
They were just way too long for a girl
like me. I honestly think that some of
this thrift store was curated. Because
what do you mean that there are this
many good tops just sitting in a row?
Then I found these adorable fold-over
denim shorts. I don't know who the
Packers are, but I love this pink
jersey. I wasn't really finding anything
else that good. Every time I find myself
getting tired of thrifting, I make my
way back over to the shoe and sock
section to get a whiff. Now I'm feeling
refreshed and satisfied with my
thrifting experience.